emedtv.com 2007-12-11

# Privacy Policy

We employ various measures to protect the privacy of those who use our site. We will strive to keep your personal information secure at all times, and will notify viewers via this web site if our data collection practices change.

**Your Responsibilities, Risks, and Rights**

  * You should be familiar with how our site works and read all of our policies. 
  * You should be aware what data is collected on this site and how it is used. 
  * You should know that this site is not intended as a substitute for medical care. Consult a healthcare professional for medical advice or treatment. 
  * You should know that this site is not intended to provide information or advice on any particular research study. Consult members of the research team for advice about a particular research study. 
  * This site is not intended for use by individuals younger than 13 years of age. 
  * You have the right to know how your information will be used and by whom. 
  * You have the right to know the information collection practices this site uses. 
  * You have the right to delete or remove your information from the site or request that we remove or delete it. 

**Overview**

Clinaero Inc, the creator of eMedTV, is committed to protecting our users' privacy. We have taken care to create a secure and safe online environment and are dedicated to privacy and confidentiality.

**Is Registration Necessary?**

Registration is not required for use of this web site. Anyone can visit the site and view the content free of charge.

**Are Web Logs Used?**

eMedTV uses standard web logs that record basic data about people who visit our web site. The following information is contained in these logs:

  * The date and time of the visit. 
  * The pages of our site viewed during the visit. 
  * The IP address of the computer used to visit the site (Computers automatically generate an IP address as they surf the Internet. Static IP addresses are potentially identifiable however dynamic IP addresses are usually not.) 
  * The type of web browser used to view our site. 
  * The web site visited immediately before coming to our site. 

We do not normally seek to identify individuals from web logs. However, web logs may be used to identify an individual who we suspect tried to damage our web site or use it in an unauthorized way. If we have reason to believe that there has been a violation of computer security or related laws, we may share our web logs with law enforcement agencies.

We use web logs as a way of conducting our own basic market research and to study how our site is being used. We will periodically analyze the web logs and use what we learn to make improvements or refinements to our web site.

**What Are Cookies? Does This Web Site Use Them?**

Cookies are packets of information that a web site transfers to a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. They are a means of keeping track of a user's preferences during a visit to a web site. In order to provide consistency, eMedTV stores a unique identifier in a temporary cookie for each site visitor.

eMedTV stores certain non-user-identifying data in "permanent" cookies. These values expire 24 hours after the last use of the eMedTV web site. They keep track of the user's current preferences regarding editorial content. If you do not want the information described above to be collected via cookies, you can turn off cookies in your browser.

No cookies are used to track an identifiable individual's movement through the site or on the Internet. They are only used to enhance the usability of the site. All medical research information may still be read with cookies turned off.

**How Can My Information Be Used?**

Data about users of the eMedTV site will never be used or disclosed for any purpose not described in this Privacy Policy. eMedTV will only use and disclose data obtained from users in the following ways:

> **Forced Legal Disclosure**
> 
> It is possible that we could be forced to disclose personally identifiable user information and personal health information in response to a search warrant, subpoena, or court order. This can happen to any record keeper. Disclosures may also be appropriate to protect our legal rights, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, to take precautions against liability, or during emergencies if physical safety is believed to be at risk. These types of disclosures are highly unlikely, but they are possible.
> 
> **Aggregate Data Use**
> 
> eMedTV may use aggregate data, derived from our web logs to study how our site is being used. We will periodically analyze this aggregate data and use what we learn to make improvements or refinements to our web site.
> 
> **Business Transfers**
> 
> As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the unlikely event that Clinaero, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets and is permissible under law.
> 
> Changes to Use and Disclosure Practices
> 
> If we make any changes to the use and disclosure of personally identifiable information, a new version of the privacy policy will be posted on the site, along with a notice alerting users to the new version. 

**Deletion and Removal of Information**

Non-identifiable information in our aggregate database will not be deleted. Like all responsible web sites, eMedTV maintains backup files as a protection against natural disasters, equipment failures, or other disruptions. Backup files protect you and us because they lessen the risk of loss of valuable data. Removing a record from our principal files does not remove that record from any of the backup systems. It may take up to six months before all information in a backup record is completely erased through the normal recycling of backup files. In the meantime, as long as backup records exist, they receive the same privacy and security protections as our other records.

**Is My Information Secure?**

Storing our data in a secure manner is essential to our business and for your protection as a user. Maintaining a secure system is in the best interests of our users and of Clinaero. Clinaero stores personally identifiable data using industry standard physical, technical, and administrative safeguards to secure data against foreseeable risks such as unauthorized use, access, disclosure, destruction, and modification. Clinaero provides users with default encryption during the transmission of their personally identifiable information-regardless of the user's browser type. Our servers are physically located in a sophisticated co-location facility.

**Protecting the Privacy of Children**

Clinaero is committed to protecting the privacy of children. We recognize and strive to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. This site is not intended for or designed to attract minors. Users under the age of 13 should not submit information to our site, and we do not collect information from any user we have reason to believe is a child under the age of 13.

**Our Accountability**

Clinaero is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We have posted this Privacy Policy to communicate the specifics of this commitment. In addition, Clinaero will address any complaints or questions that our users may have regarding this policy or its implementation. If you have a complaint or question about our Privacy Policy please send e-mail to privacy@clinaero.com. Alternatively, you can send a letter to the following address:

Clinaero, Inc

PO Box 1255

Bellevue, WA 98009

Attn: Privacy Officer

Last reviewed/updated November 26, 2007
